<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Victoria Ashman Photography</title>
    <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Victoria Ashman Photography</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>North Wales Photography trip</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/newpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/newpost/</guid>
      <description>TEST I have recently signed a three-year contract to join Arcangel, a creative stock photography agency. I’m mainly interested in producing photographs that will end up on book covers, and I hope that this is a fruitful endeavour.
 But, goodness has it been challenging. I have submitted 42 pictures so far and only 12 have been accepted. Rejection is difficult, but as it turns out is quite common at Arcangel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archangel Creative Stock Photography</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/archangel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/archangel/</guid>
      <description>I have recently signed a three-year contract to join Arcangel, a creative stock photography agency. I’m mainly interested in producing photographs that will end up on book covers, and I hope that this is a fruitful endeavour.
But, goodness has it been challenging. I have submitted 42 pictures so far and only 12 have been accepted. Rejection is difficult, but as it turns out is quite common at Arcangel. They have a high rejection rate (as they only accept the best imagery to keep their image library strong), which is no bad thing for the photographer and the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaeological sites in the local area</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/archaeological/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/archaeological/</guid>
      <description>I am nine months post-transplant. I would love to say that it’s been an easy ride, that I instantly felt amazing. Well, actually I did, but I think this had a lot to do with the initial high dose of steroids, the incredible high at being alive and the instant easing of the strain of kidney failure. As steroids were weaned down (to my maintenance dose), I started to struggle – there was a realisation that this would not be a smooth ride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative imagery at Arcangel</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/featured3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/featured3/</guid>
      <description>I recently signed a 3 year contract with Arcangel. They specialise in book covers and I am trying to focus on imagery with book covers in mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prints</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/featured2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/featured2/</guid>
      <description>Fine Art America enables you to buy prints. Click the link below to go to my Fine Art America portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Images</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/featured1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/featured1/</guid>
      <description>You can find my stock images for sale on my Adobe stock portfolio. The site has new content added all the time. Thank you for viewing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/life/</guid>
      <description>Just over two months ago, I had my transplant! It’s been both an amazing time, and at points very difficult – due to the horrible word rejection and a near hospital readmission. It has been beyond what I could have possibly imagined. It’s also been quite lonely. I’ve been shielding and so my normal support network (apart from Darren), have not been able to help me like they would have done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh Life</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/oh-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/oh-life/</guid>
      <description>So, I thought I’d should give a progress report. I am better, but life is still challenging and unfortunately for me it’s painful the majority of the time.
I thought the best way to show you a glimpse into my life would be to write about a typical day. I wake up at 7.30, have breakfast and then get onto dialysis just before 8. When its not painful I can be off dialysis and clearing up at about 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, thank you for taking the time to read about me and visit my website, my name is Victoria.
My love of photography started after I became unwell. This changed my attitude in many ways but really it taught me to see the beauty around me. I was at Bangor university at the time – on the doorstep of Snowdonia and this combined with the nature of my studies gave me a real appreciation for my surroundings, and so developed my first love… landscape photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>I am now mainly focusing on book covers, stock photography and landscape photography and can be contacted by email below. I will reply as soon as possible.
Many thanks, Victoria
Email: va.photography@hotmail.co.uk
Contact Me @ va.photography@hotmail.co.uk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Stock Image Libraries AlamyiStock PhotoAdobe StockShutterstock Other Websites RedbubbleI have sold my photographs at Redbubble for years, you can buy wall art, phone cases, stationery and lots more
HobbyHelpA fellow photographer’s very comprehensive guide to photography for beginners… definitely worth a read
Pricelis Art LtdPricelis art are Lis and Dave Price, they are printers and award winning framers and conveniently they are located right next to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Store</title>
      <link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/store/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
