<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lifestyle on Victoria Ashman Photography</title><link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/tags/lifestyle/</link><description>Recent content in lifestyle on Victoria Ashman Photography</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/tags/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>North Wales Photography trip</title><link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/north-wales/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/north-wales/</guid><description>Lake Ogwin
In July, we went to North Wales for a landscape photography trip. The trip was important to me for many reasons. I went to Bangor University, and I loved my time up there, really feeling like I had found my home. I had not been back to Bangor for ten years due to ill-health - so a trip was long overdue. North Wales has the most beautiful landscapes, so it is a must for landscape photographers.</description></item><item><title>Life</title><link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/life-after/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/life-after/</guid><description>Just over two months ago, I had my transplant! It’s been both an amazing time, and at points very difficult – due to the horrible word rejection and a near hospital readmission. It has been beyond what I could have possibly imagined. It’s also been quite lonely. I’ve been shielding and so my normal support network (apart from Darren), have not been able to help me like they would have done.</description></item><item><title>Oh Life</title><link>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/oh-life/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://victoriaashmanphotography.github.io/posts/oh-life/</guid><description>So, I thought I’d should give a progress report. I am better, but life is still challenging and unfortunately for me it’s painful the majority of the time.
I thought the best way to show you a glimpse into my life would be to write about a typical day. I wake up at 7.30, have breakfast and then get onto dialysis just before 8. When its not painful I can be off dialysis and clearing up at about 8.</description></item></channel></rss>